Hello.
I have a question for you:
Have you got something you're the best at?
Not just good or better than your friends at,
but the best of all?
I can draw and paint quite well.
But some of my friends are better than me.
And my friend Joan, well, she's the most amazing painter!
I can play the piano very well.
But my friend Carlos plays better than me.
But, definitely, my friend Amelie is the best of all of us!
And she is the fastest player, too.
I'm pretty good at most things.
But I guess the only thing I'm the best at
is having the best friends!
OK. Let me know if you're the best at anything!
Leave a note in the comments. Bye.
Which language does the vlogger use?
We use superlative adjectives to compare more than two things.
To form the superlative of short adjectives, we use the plus –est.
And she's the fastest player, too.
To form the superlative of long adjectives,
we use the most plus adjective.
Well, she's the most amazing painter!
The best and the worst are irregular adjectives.
Have you got something you're the best at?
Use it!
Change the sentences to use superlatives.
He's the fastest rider.
Now you try.
He is the tallest of his brothers.
She is the most amazing singer.
The apple is the healthiest snack.